I've been in an unknown city with a real in
my pocket and ninety days to set up a business.
I live inside the Chevette and today is the twentieth.
I made that whole investment in the Uber 1 dog car,
but now I need to find a way to publicize this.
1st step is on Instagram
here.
Bold just showed up here.
Oh,
with the family and we're planning a walk with them.
And is found out
it's 0 huh? bro
guys liked my job where they gave me more
flyers to be able to make my grill is a lie,
bro.
I thought I lost it at the chevas,
Man, man,
thanks bro bye,
all the good things for you were worth.
The guy said that to his man.
If you want,
I know a guy over there who you can give him a flyer.
It's also from another missile and bro my phone.
You see how cool it is,
you do a nice job for someone,
you end up having more opportunities with what you're doing,
you never know who you're looking at crazy
my brother says and then my brother,
how are you,
how are you today,
how are you, and then,
girls, how are you?
I'm disclosing 1 new,
there will be 1 new,
I don't know if you know,
you know in anxiety.
It was even nice for you to relate.
Do Network,
right?
I wanted to ask you if I could leave some flyers here.
All right,
leave here a little for the crowd to see.
Bye, Debora,
too much from the heart was worth it.
And that's it,
Dude,
then you're going to rebuild this relationship base,
it gets easier if you're more strategic about what you're doing old,
you optimize your time and effort.
That little brother Ali looks like me.
.
I received 1 very good old job proposal 1 very
good possibility I'll be happy until tomorrow.